<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Welcome To My Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome To My Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan garia)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan garia)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.pawangaria.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Capture Full page Screenshots using Chrome Browser</title>
      <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/capturefullscreenshotinchrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan garia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/capturefullscreenshotinchrome/</guid>
      <description>While working everyone feels the need of taking full-page screenshots but Its always hard to take the full page screenshot as normal screenshot works on the page area which is in the frame. Like on Mac we use Command + Shift + 4 and select the area and take the screenshot but in this method, we can not scroll down and take the part hidden in the screenshot. Like I took a screenshot of BBC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy and host your website on Google Firebase</title>
      <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/deployyourwebsiteonfirebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan garia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/deployyourwebsiteonfirebase/</guid>
      <description>After finishing the first draft of my new website I wanted to host my website on firebase because I found Firebaseas hosting server very useful, easy to use and free of cost for limited hosting.
So I decided to write down my knowdledge and experience of hosting website with firebase here and if you are also looking for hosting your website in firebase please follow thesteps below.
Create account or Login on Firebase Console To deploy your website on firebase first you need to create an account on Google Firebase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Firebase custom domain mapping with GoDaddy</title>
      <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/mapcustomdomainwithgodaddyandfirebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan garia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/mapcustomdomainwithgodaddyandfirebase/</guid>
      <description>In my last post, I explained about hosting our website on Google Firebase and we are able to access the website using the firebase Url. Now in this article, we are going to talk and learn about adding our website with custom domain like your own domains purchased on the domain providing websites like GoDaddy and NameCheap. I this article we are going to integrate our domain in GoDaddy with Firebase hosted website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrate TestRail with Automated TestCases in Java&#43;TestNG</title>
      <link>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/testrailwithjavaintegration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>pawangaria@gmail.com (Pawan garia)</author>
      <guid>https://www.pawangaria.com/post/testrailwithjavaintegration/</guid>
      <description>What is TestRail? TestRail (http://www.gurock.com/testrail/) is a modern and very nice tool for the Test Case Management by Quality Assurance and Development Team. TestManagement tools are very helpful for managing the test cases and TestRail is pack with very useful features like web-based application, Rest API integration etc.
Why to use TestManagement Tool with Automation? While making Regression or any kind of Test Automation suit there is a need of maintaining Use cases and maintain the repository which anyone can access and see what use cases are been automated and what is left.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>